Guide to the Committee to Frame a World Constitution Records 1945-1951
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Meeting Minutes
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 15 April, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 15-16 April, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 16 April, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings, New York, 17-18 May, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 18-19 June, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, New York, 19-20 July, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, New York, 16-17 August, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 24-25 Oct., 1946 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Notes on February Meeting., 1947 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 6 Feb., 1947 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 7 Feb., 1947 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 1 April, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 2 April, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 14 July, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 14 July, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings, Chicago, 15 July, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 6)